{
    "subject": "resource/Matti_Manushulu",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1990_films",
    "human_readable": "Matti Manushulu is about 1990 films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8080865740776062,
            "question": "Around what year were Matti Manushulu's films made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533406615257263,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about Matti Manushulu and their films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7469767332077026,
            "question": "Is there a specific genre that Matti Manushulu's films are known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6688036918640137,
            "question": "What is the approximate decade of Matti Manushulu's film career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.638122022151947,
            "question": "What is Matti Manushulu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.631480872631073,
            "question": "Could you tell me more about Matti Manushulu's filmography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799094438552856,
            "question": "What impact did Matti Manushulu have on the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4963914155960083,
            "question": "Has Matti Manushulu won any awards for their films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43129000067710876,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors or directors associated with Matti Manushulu's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3945038616657257,
            "question": "What type of work is associated with Matti Manushulu?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Matti Manushulu is about 1990 films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4741_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors or directors associated with Matti Manushulu's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4741_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Matti Manushulu won any awards for their films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4741_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Matti Manushulu have on the film industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4741_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4741_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`\n\nThe documents mention that \"Matti Manushulu is a 1990 Telugu drama film\", indicating that Matti Manushulu indeed refers to a 1990 film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Matti Manushulu is about 1990 films.\" Specifically, document `72.txt` states it was a 1990 Telugu drama film, and `84.txt` provides details including its release date on January 1, 1990."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}